[
  {
    "question": "apple",
    "answer": "Manzana"
  },
  {
    "question": "traffic light",
    "answer": "Sem√°foro"
  },
  {
    "question": "strawberry",
    "answer": "Fresa"
  },
  {
    "question": "orange",
    "answer": "Naranja"
  },
  {
    "question": "horse",
    "answer": "Caballo"
  },
  {
    "question": "handcuffs",
    "answer": "Esposas"
  },
  {
    "question": "travel",
    "answer": "Viajar"
  },
  {
    "question": "pistol (gun)",
    "answer": "Pistola"
  },
  {
    "question": "rocket (space travel)",
    "answer": "Cohete"
  },
  {
    "question": "calculator",
    "answer": "Calculadora"
  }
]